<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Trainings on Songlaa Kubernetes Security Trainings</title><link>https://songlaa.com/trainings/</link><description>Recent content in Trainings on Songlaa Kubernetes Security Trainings</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://songlaa.com/trainings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction to Kubernetes, the secure way</title><link>https://songlaa.com/trainings/kubernetes-fundamentals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://songlaa.com/trainings/kubernetes-fundamentals/</guid><description>Overview This training provides a comprehensive foundation for Kubernetes with a strong emphasis on security:
Basic concepts (Grundkonzepte) Kubernetes architecture and components Application deployment Service layer and discovery Storage in Kubernetes Resource types (StatefulSet, DaemonSet, Job, ConfigMap) Resource management in Kubernetes Troubleshooting Network Policies Security Context Overview: Cloud Native Computing Landscape Training Format: Onsite training at your location
Audience Beginners or professionals who want to understand Kubernetes fundamentals.
Duration 1-2 days</description></item><item><title>Kubernetes Security Deep Dive</title><link>https://songlaa.com/trainings/kubernetes-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://songlaa.com/trainings/kubernetes-security/</guid><description>Overview Comprehensive security training covering:
Introduction and basic concepts (Container &amp;amp; Kubernetes) Kubernetes and Network Security Pod Security Context Cloud Native Security and Kubernetes (Image Building &amp;amp; Deployment) Controlling Access to the Kube API / Admission Control RBAC (Role-Based Access Control) Observability &amp;amp; Runtime Security Training Format: Onsite training at your location
Audience DevOps, SRE, security engineers, and IT teams.
Duration 1–2 days
Requirements Participants only need:
Their laptop Direct internet connection Outcome Participants will understand and implement Kubernetes security best practices, policies, and controls.</description></item></channel></rss>